# **Thor Wessel Lindberg**

## CONTACT

Copenhagen, Denmark thorlindberg@icloud.com

thorlindberg.com apple.com/developer/thor-lindberg

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a 25-year old junior developer and digital designer, passionate about design systems, software architecture, and mobile applications.

For the past 4+ years I have been writing in object-oriented programming languages, and the past 1+ year I have been developing eventand state-driven software projects.

# **LANGUAGES**

Swift, JSX, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, Java, Visual Basic for Applications, Lua, SQL, XML

#### **TOOLS**

Xcode, Visual Studio Code, Git, GitLab, MATLAB, Figma, Excel, Tableau, Cytoscape

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

CSS, SwiftUI, UIKit, Streamlit, React, Bootstrap

## **EDUCATION**

MSc Information Technology (cand.it)

IT-University of Copenhagen, 2020-2022

BSc Health Information Science (bach.sund.it) Copenhagen University, 2017-2020

#### **EXPERIENCE**

IT Administrator, Financial Intelligence Unit Special Crime Unit, 2021-2022

Assistant Lecturer, Introduction to Programming *IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022* 

Assistant Lecturer, UX Design II IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Teaching Assistant, UX Design I IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Teaching Assistant, Experimental Design IT-University of Copenhagen, 2022

Teaching Assistant, Introduction to Programming *IT-University of Copenhagen, 2021* 

Store Leader, Domino's Pizza Domino's Lyngby, 2021-2022